Thomas G. Paterson Papers
© 2003 University of Connecticut
- Series VII: Photographs, negatives and microfiche, undated, 1944-1968
  - Photographs
    - Contesting Castro: photos for illustration of book, undated, 1954-1961 (Box 29:776)
    - Texaco and Cuba: photos of Texaco refinery at Santiago de Cuba, undated, 1960 (Box 29:777)
  - Negatives
    - American Foreign Policy (1st ed.), undated (Box 29:778)
    - Mersfelder, Ade: negatives of sketches of World War II prisoners, undated, 1944-1945 (Box 29:779)
  - Microfiche
    - Documents from Foreign Office Correspondence (FO371), Public Records Office, London, England, 1945 (Box 29:780)